{
  "openingRemarks": "NB: you have to give answers as simplified fractions.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{68}{7} \\div \\dfrac{-8}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-51/14",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [14]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-21}{10} \\times \\dfrac{-1}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "21/80",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [80]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-23}{2} \\times 0\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-23}{4} \\times \\dfrac{-27}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "621/20",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [20]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-11}{4} \\times 9\\)",
      "answer": "-99/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-48}{7} \\div -3\\)",
      "answer": "16/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-38}{5} \\times \\dfrac{-51}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "969/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{71}{3} \\times \\dfrac{-73}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-5183/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 \\times \\dfrac{-29}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "-87/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-19}{2} \\div \\dfrac{-77}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "95/77",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [77]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{7} \\times \\dfrac{-36}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-216/35",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [35]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-17}{3} \\times \\dfrac{-2}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "34/21",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [21]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{24}{11} \\div -26\\)",
      "answer": "-12/143",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [143]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-6 \\div \\dfrac{16}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-15/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-41}{6} \\times -11\\)",
      "answer": "451/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(11 \\times \\dfrac{97}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1067/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-47}{5} \\times \\dfrac{-1}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "47/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-25}{2} \\div \\dfrac{-83}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "275/166",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [166]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{41}{8} \\div \\dfrac{67}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "41/268",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [268]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{77}{4} \\times \\dfrac{-16}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-308/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{100}{9} \\div \\dfrac{17}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "100/51",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [51]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\div \\dfrac{25}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "8/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{91}{9} \\div \\dfrac{-49}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-13/21",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [21]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{33}{4} \\div \\dfrac{-29}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-99/116",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [116]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-40 \\div \\dfrac{52}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-30/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [13]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-49}{12} \\div \\dfrac{-53}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "245/636",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [636]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-23}{6} \\times \\dfrac{31}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-713/18",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [18]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-16}{5} \\div \\dfrac{25}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "-128/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [125]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-28 \\div \\dfrac{-43}{12}\\)",
      "answer": "336/43",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [43]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-78}{7} \\div 16\\)",
      "answer": "-39/56",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [56]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{85}{4} \\div \\dfrac{-47}{12}\\)",
      "answer": "-255/47",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [47]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{47}{10} \\div \\dfrac{38}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "47/76",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [76]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-31}{10} \\div 7\\)",
      "answer": "-31/70",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [70]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-47}{3} \\div \\dfrac{7}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-188/21",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [21]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-45}{2} \\div \\dfrac{-43}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "45/43",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [43]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(18 \\times \\dfrac{73}{12}\\)",
      "answer": "219/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-9 \\times \\dfrac{-73}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "657/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [11]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-27}{5} \\div \\dfrac{-3}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "63/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-73}{5} \\div \\dfrac{61}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-73/61",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [61]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{7} \\times \\dfrac{4}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "8/77",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [77]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{8} \\times -13\\)",
      "answer": "13/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-91}{2} \\times \\dfrac{47}{12}\\)",
      "answer": "-4277/24",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [24]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-4}{3} \\div \\dfrac{14}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-10/21",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [21]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{67}{11} \\div -14\\)",
      "answer": "-67/154",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [154]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{5} \\times -12\\)",
      "answer": "-276/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{77}{9} \\div \\dfrac{-1}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "-77",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{38}{7} \\times \\dfrac{-84}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-456/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-52}{5} \\div \\dfrac{-2}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "286/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{98}{11} \\div \\dfrac{-92}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-245/506",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [506]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-54}{7} \\div \\dfrac{92}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-135/322",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [322]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-23}{4} \\times 48\\)",
      "answer": "-276",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(13 \\times \\dfrac{-4}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-52/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-2 \\times \\dfrac{-38}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "76/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-12 \\times \\dfrac{89}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "-178",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{4} \\times \\dfrac{14}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-7/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{11} \\times \\dfrac{-19}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-76/55",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [55]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-80}{3} \\div \\dfrac{-78}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "200/117",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [117]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-53}{6} \\times -8\\)",
      "answer": "212/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-35}{12} \\div \\dfrac{-94}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "35/376",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [376]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-42}{5} \\div \\dfrac{-62}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "21/31",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [31]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{35}{9} \\times \\dfrac{36}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "28",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-22}{3} \\times \\dfrac{-1}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "22/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [27]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-17}{3} \\times \\dfrac{-69}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "391/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{63}{5} \\times \\dfrac{76}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "1596/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{3} \\div \\dfrac{93}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-11/279",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [279]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{6} \\div 15\\)",
      "answer": "11/90",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [90]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-5}{8} \\div 25\\)",
      "answer": "-1/40",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [40]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-62 \\div \\dfrac{73}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-434/73",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [73]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-74}{3} \\div \\dfrac{11}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-148/33",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [33]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{3} \\div 22\\)",
      "answer": "1/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{53}{4} \\div \\dfrac{-68}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-371/272",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [272]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{8} \\times \\dfrac{23}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "253/32",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [32]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-4}{7} \\div \\dfrac{-66}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "2/33",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [33]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-49}{5} \\times \\dfrac{-81}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "3969/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(28 \\div \\dfrac{-98}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-22/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-77}{3} \\div \\dfrac{69}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "-616/207",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [207]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{29}{2} \\times \\dfrac{-83}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "-2407/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [12]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{2} \\times \\dfrac{11}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "55/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-93}{2} \\div \\dfrac{69}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-341/46",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [46]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-4}{3} \\times 42\\)",
      "answer": "-56",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{2} \\times \\dfrac{11}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "77/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{94}{5} \\div -5\\)",
      "answer": "-94/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(40 \\times \\dfrac{-3}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-24",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-92}{3} \\times \\dfrac{-33}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "1012/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{86}{7} \\div \\dfrac{-3}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-344/21",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [21]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-30 \\times \\dfrac{-89}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "445",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [1, 0]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{57}{2} \\div 7\\)",
      "answer": "57/14",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [14]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{43}{7} \\times \\dfrac{40}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "1720/77",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [77]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{61}{2} \\times \\dfrac{-82}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-2501/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-66 \\div \\dfrac{-54}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "121/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-31}{9} \\times -3\\)",
      "answer": "31/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-4}{5} \\div -48\\)",
      "answer": "1/60",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [60]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-2}{3} \\times \\dfrac{81}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-27/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-41}{2} \\div \\dfrac{55}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "-369/110",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [110]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{91}{6} \\div \\dfrac{38}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "1001/228",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [228]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-95}{11} \\times \\dfrac{-26}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "2470/99",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [99]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-35}{6} \\div \\dfrac{65}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "-28/39",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [39]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-95}{9} \\times \\dfrac{33}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-1045/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-23}{3} \\div -21\\)",
      "answer": "23/63",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [63]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-86}{7} \\times \\dfrac{29}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "-1247/21",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [21]
    }
  ]
}
